<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notes of another software engineer on peyman.blog</title><link>https://peyman.blog/</link><description>Recent content in Notes of another software engineer on peyman.blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:49:30 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://peyman.blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Structures in Python</title><link>https://peyman.blog/posts/data-structures-in-python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:49:30 +0330</pubDate><guid>https://peyman.blog/posts/data-structures-in-python/</guid><description>When we code in Python usually there are multiple data structures such as list, tuple, set, and dict that we mostly use. But besides these four, Python has other data structures that each of them like those four has some strengths and weaknesses based on their implementation and structure that we can use, and it&amp;rsquo;s better to know them because sometimes it might help and have a better performance and features based on your problem than list, tuple, set, and dict.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://peyman.blog/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://peyman.blog/pages/about/</guid><description>My name is Peyman Salehi. I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer.
Most of my experiences are in back-end development. Besides that, I&amp;rsquo;m very enthusiastic about system engineering and spend my free time researching and learning more about it.
In my blog, I mostly write about what I learn or experience in my job, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually related to software engineering, programming languages, Linux, open-source software, and tools I use.
And finally, I&amp;rsquo;m working in tech to make things easier for ourselves, not doing weird stuff!</description></item></channel></rss>